Guide to the Human Service Employees Registration and Voter Education Fund (Human SERVE) records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XXV: Federal Legislation
  - House: Congressional Record, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1286)
  - House: Hearing, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1287)
  - House - HR 2 Legislation, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1288)
  - House - HR 2 Amendments, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1289)
  - House - HR 2 Grassroots/Swift, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1290)
  - House - HR 2 Vote, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1291)
  - House - HR 2 Conference Reports, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1292)
  - House - HR 2 Opposition, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1293)
  - House/Senate: Advocacy/Grassroots, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 1294)
  - House/Senate, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 1295)
  - House/Senate - S 1888, HR 3666 Cranston/Conyers, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 1296)
  - House/Senate: Grassroots, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 1297)
  - House/Senate - S 2061, HR 3950 Grassroots, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 1298)
  - House/Senate - S 2061, HR 3950, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 1299)
  - House/Senate - HR 15, HR 17 Grassroots, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1300)
  - House/Senate - S 874, HR 2190 Grassroots, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1301)
  - House/Senate - S 874, HR 2190 Grassroots, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1302)
  - House/Senate: Language to Remove Prohibition, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1303)
  - House/Senate - S 250 Grassroots, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 1304)
  - House/Senate - HR 2, S 460 Legislation, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1305)
  - House/Senate - HR 2, S 460, S 2 Grassroots, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1306)
  - House/Senate - HR 2, S 460 Conference, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1307)
  - Grassroots - General, 1986-1988 (Box 30, Folder 1308)
  - Grassroots - General, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1309)
  - Grassroots - General, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 1310)
  - Press, [No Dates] (Box 30, Folder 1311)
  - Press, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 1312)
  - Press, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 1313)
  - Press, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 1314)
  - Press, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1315)
  - Press, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 1316)
  - Press, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 1317)
  - Press: Op-Ed, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 1318)
  - Press: Negative, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 1319)
  - Press: Release, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 1320)
  - Press NVRA, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 1321)
  - Press: State Non-Compliance, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 1322)
  - Post-NVRA Opposition: Committee on House Oversight Hearing, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 1323)
  - Post-NVRA Opposition: Secretary of State Amendments, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 1324)
  - Post-NVRA Opposition: Anti-NVRA, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 1325)
  - Post-NVRA Opposition: Coalition, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 1326)
  - Post-NVRA Opposition: Coalition Response to Anti-NVRA Amendments, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 1327)
  - Post-NVRA Legislative Efforts, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 1328)
  - Post-NVRA Legislative Efforts, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 1329)
  - Post-NVRA Legislative Efforts, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 1330)
  - Post-NVRA Legislative Efforts, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 1331)
  - Post-NVRA Legislative Efforts, January 1998 (Box 31, Folder 1332)
  - Post-NVRA Legislative Efforts, February 1998-March 1998 (Box 31, Folder 1333)
  - Post-NVRA Legislative Efforts, April 1998-December 1998 (Box 31, Folder 1334)
  - Topics Address Confirmation (Box 31, Folder 1335)
  - Topics Chronology of Developments, 1965-1994 (Box 31, Folder 1336)
  - Topics Citizenship (Box 31, Folder 1337)
  - Topics Civil Rights Data (Box 31, Folder 1338)
  - Topics Civil Rights Debate within Coalition (Box 31, Folder 1339)
  - Topics College Campus (Box 31, Folder 1340)
  - Topics Confidentiality (Box 31, Folder 1341)
  - Topics Constitutionality (Box 31, Folder 1342)
  - Topics Costs (Box 31, Folder 1343)
  - Topics Data Drivers' Licenses and Welfare (Box 31, Folder 1344)
  - Topics Declinations (Box 31, Folder 1345)
  - Topics Department of Justice (Box 31, Folder 1346)
  - Topics Document Retention (Box 31, Folder 1347)
  - Topics Dual Lists (Box 31, Folder 1348)
  - Topics Election Day Registration Exemption (Box 31, Folder 1349)
  - Topics Fail Safe Voting (Box 31, Folder 1350)
  - Topics Fraud (Box 31, Folder 1351)
  - Topics Identification at the Polls (Box 31, Folder 1352)
  - Topics Internal Memos (Box 31, Folder 1353)
  - Topics Legislative Chronology, 1971-1995 (Box 31, Folder 1354)
  - Topics Multi-lingual (Box 31, Folder 1355)
  - Topics National Change of Address (Box 31, Folder 1356)
  - Topics Person vs. Individual (Box 31, Folder 1357)
  - Topics Postal Rate Reduction (Box 31, Folder 1358)
  - Topics Purging, 1985-1988 (Box 31, Folder 1359)
  - Topics Purging, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 1360)
  - Topics Purging, 1991-1993 (Box 31, Folder 1361)
  - Topics Secretary of State Ralph Munro (Box 31, Folder 1362)
  - Topics Social Security Numbers (Box 31, Folder 1363)
  - Topics State Constitutional Conflicts (Box 31, Folder 1364)
  - Topics Tenth Amendment (Box 31, Folder 1365)
  - Topics Unfunded Mandates (Box 32, Folder 1366)
  - White House: President Carter, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 1367)
  - White House: Clinton, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 1368)
  - White House: Bush Veto, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 1369)
  - White House NVRA Veto/Reaction (Box 32, Folder 1370)
  - White House, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 1371)
  - White House: Signing, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 1372)
  - White House: Signing Photographs, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 1373)
  - White House: Executive Orders, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 1374)
  - White House, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 1375)
  - White House, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 1376)
- Series XXVI: Federal Agencies
  - Summary (Box 32, Folder 1377)
  - Department of Agriculture (Box 32, Folder 1378)
  - Department of Agriculture WIC and WIC Exemption (Box 32, Folder 1379)
  - Census Bureau (Box 32, Folder 1380)
  - Congressional Budget Office (Box 32, Folder 1381)
  - Congressional Research Service (Box 32, Folder 1382)
  - Congressional Research Service Dispute, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 1383)
  - Department of Defense (Box 32, Folder 1384)
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development (Box 32, Folder 1385)
  - Department of Labor (Box 32, Folder 1386)
  - General Accounting Office (Box 32, Folder 1387)
  - Head Start (Box 32, Folder 1388)
  - Health and Human Services (Box 32, Folder 1389)
  - Health and Human Services: Aid to Families with Dependent Children (AFDC) (Box 32, Folder 1390)
  - Health Care Financing Administration (Medicaid) (Box 32, Folder 1391)
  - Federal Election Commission Mail-In forms (Box 32, Folder 1392)
  - Federal Election Commission, 1986-1992 (Box 32, Folder 1393)
  - Federal Election Commission, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 1394)
  - Federal Election Commission Ad Hoc Discussion Group, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 1395)
  - Federal Election Commission Advisory Panel Annual Meeting, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 1396)
  - Federal Election Commission Rule Making/Final Rules, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 1397)
  - Federal Election Commission, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 1398)
  - Federal Election Commission Ad Hoc Discussion Group, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 1399)
  - Federal Election Commission Advisory Panel Annual Meeting, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 1400)
  - Federal Election Commission Rule Making/Final Rules, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 1401)
  - Federal Election Commission Report, 1992-1994 (Box 32, Folder 1402)
  - Federal Election Commission, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 1403)
  - Federal Election Commission Implementation Problems/Solution Report, 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 1404)
  - Federal Election Commission Report, 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 1405)
  - Federal Election Commission, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 1406)
  - Federal Election Commission, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 1407)
  - Federal Election Commission Report, 1997-1998 (Box 33, Folder 1408)
  - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS) (Box 33, Folder 1409)
  - Office of Personnel Management Donald Devine Controversy (Box 33, Folder 1410)
  - President's Management Council (Box 33, Folder 1411)
- Series XXVII: NVRA Implementation
  - Human SERVE Reports 1 Month, March 1995 (Box 33, Folder 1412)
  - Human SERVE Reports 3 Months, May 1995 (Box 33, Folder 1413)
  - Human SERVE Reports 4 Months, June 1995 (Box 33, Folder 1414)
  - Human SERVE Reports 6 Months, August 1995 (Box 33, Folder 1415)
  - Human SERVE Reports 9 Months, November 1995 (Box 33, Folder 1416)
  - Human SERVE Reports 1 Year, February 1996 (Box 33, Folder 1417)
  - Human SERVE Reports 18 Months, July 1996 (Box 33, Folder 1418)
  - Human SERVE Reports 18 Month Survey, July 1996 (Box 33, Folder 1419)
  - Human SERVE Reports Summaries (Box 33, Folder 1420)
  - Public Assistance Agency Monitoring (Box 33, Folder 1421)
  - Public Assistance Alerts (Box 33, Folder 1422)
  - Public Assistance American Public Welfare Association Conference (Box 33, Folder 1423)
  - Public Assistance "Implementation Watch" and Monitoring Kit (Box 33, Folder 1424)
  - Public Assistance Monitoring, 1997 - 1998 (Box 33, Folder 1425)
  - Public Assistance State Social Services Profiles (Box 33, Folder 1426)
  - Public Assistance Welfare Combined Forms (Box 33, Folder 1427)
  - Public Assistance Welfare Forms Alabama-Illinois (Box 33, Folder 1428)
  - Public Assistance Welfare Forms Iowa-Michigan (Box 33, Folder 1429)
  - Public Assistance Welfare Forms Minnesota-Oklahoma (Box 33, Folder 1430)
  - Public Assistance Welfare Forms Oregon-Wyoming (Box 33, Folder 1431)
  - State by State Centralized Voter Registration (Box 33, Folder 1432)
  - State by State Labor Department Profiles (Box 33, Folder 1433)
  - State by State Targeted States (Box 33, Folder 1434)
  - State by State Task Forces (Box 33, Folder 1435)
  - State by State Updates/Reports Multi-State (Box 33, Folder 1436)
  - State by State Updates Arkansas-West Virginia (Box 33, Folder 1437)
  - Topics Articles (Box 33, Folder 1438)
  - Topics Colleges/Universities (Box 33, Folder 1439)
  - Topics Congressional Black Caucus (Box 33, Folder 1440)
  - Topics D.C. Coalition Meetings Notes/Agendas (Box 33, Folder 1441)
  - Topics Disabilities (Box 33, Folder 1442)
  - Topics: Election Administrators Conference, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 1443)
  - Topics Election Day Problems (Box 33, Folder 1444)
  - Topics Election Day Registration (Box 33, Folder 1445)
  - Topics Fiscal Impacts/Costs (Box 33, Folder 1446)
  - Topics Fraud/Costs/Unfunded Mandates (Box 33, Folder 1447)
  - Topics Internal Memos (Box 34, Folder 1448)
  - Topics League of Women Voters Conference (Box 34, Folder 1449)
  - Topics League of Women Voters Updates (Box 34, Folder 1450)
  - Topics Mail-in Registration (Box 34, Folder 1451)
  - Topics Montjoy Survey (Box 34, Folder 1452)
  - Topics Overviews (Box 34, Folder 1453)
  - Topics Preclearance (Box 34, Folder 1454)
  - Topics Problems (Box 34, Folder 1455)
  - Topics Results/Data (Box 34, Folder 1456)
  - Topics Senator Bradley Letter (Box 34, Folder 1457)
  - Topics State Attorneys General (Box 34, Folder 1458)
  - Topics White House (Box 34, Folder 1459)
  - Topics Women (Box 34, Folder 1460)
- Series XXVIII: Legal Restraints
  - Pre-NVRA Arkansas (Box 34, Folder 1461)
  - Pre-NVRA California (Box 34, Folder 1462)
  - Pre-NVRA Connecticut (Box 34, Folder 1463)
  - Pre-NVRA Florida (Box 34, Folder 1464)
  - Pre-NVRA Illinois (Box 34, Folder 1465)
  - Pre-NVRA Iowa (Box 34, Folder 1466)
  - Pre-NVRA Massachusetts (Box 34, Folder 1467)
  - Pre-NVRA Michigan (Box 34, Folder 1468)
  - Pre-NVRA Mississippi (Box 34, Folder 1469)
  - Pre-NVRA Missouri (Box 34, Folder 1470)
  - Pre-NVRA New Hampshire (Box 34, Folder 1471)
  - Pre-NVRA New Jersey (Box 34, Folder 1472)
  - Pre-NVRA North Carolina (Box 34, Folder 1473)
  - Pre-NVRA Ohio (Box 34, Folder 1474)
  - Pre-NVRA Pennsylvania (Box 34, Folder 1475)
  - Pre-NVRA South Dakota (Box 34, Folder 1476)
  - Pre-NVRA Human SERVE Legal Program, 1989-1991 (a) (Box 34, Folder 1477)
  - Pre-NVRA Human SERVE Legal Program, 1989-1991 (b) (Box 34, Folder 1478)
  - Pre-NVRA Litigation, Memos, 1980s (Box 34, Folder 1479)
  - Pre-NVRA Voting Rights/Election Law Reporter (Box 34, Folder 1480)
  - Pre-NVRA ACORN Campaigns, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 1481)
  - Pre-NVRA Voting Rights Act (Box 34, Folder 1482)
  - National Mobilization/Litigation Campaign, January 1984-June 1984 (Box 34, Folder 1483)
  - National Mobilization/Litigation Campaign, July 1984-February 1985 (Box 34, Folder 1484)
  - National Mobilization/Litigation Campaign National Meeting: Emergency Mobilization on the Right to Vote, June 13, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 1485)
  - National Mobilization/Litigation Campaign, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 1486)
  - National Mobilization/Litigation Campaign Preparation Strategy Conference on Voter Registration, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 1487)
  - National Mobilization/Litigation Campaign Strategy Conference on Voter Registration, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 1488)
  - National Mobilization/Litigation Campaign Post-Strategy Conference on Voter Registration, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 1489)
  - National Mobilization/Litigation Campaign, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 1490)
  - National Mobilization/Litigation Campaign, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1491)
  - National Mobilization/Litigation Campaign San Antonio Conference, October 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1492)
  - National Mobilization/Litigation Campaign, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 1493)
  - Post-NVRA Human SERVE Litigation Updates (Box 35, Folder 1494)
  - Post-NVRA Network Memos #1 (Box 35, Folder 1495)
  - Post-NVRA Network Memos #2 (Box 35, Folder 1496)
  - Post-NVRA State Non-Compliance (Box 35, Folder 1497)
  - Post-NVRA Department of Justice (Box 35, Folder 1498)
  - Post-NVRA Media/Press Release (Box 35, Folder 1499)
  - Post-NVRA Disabilities (Box 35, Folder 1500)
  - Conference Manual #1, October, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 1501)
  - Conference Manual #2, October, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 1502)
  - Conference Manual #3, October, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 1503)
  - Conference Preparation, October, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 1504)
  - Conference Preparation-State Questionnaire, October, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 1505)
  - Conference Proceedings, October, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 1506)
  - Federal Grant Restrictions Hatch Act (Box 35, Folder 1507)
  - Federal Grant Restrictions Various, 1981-1989 (Box 36, Folder 1508)
  - Federal Grant Restrictions Various, 1990-1996 (Box 36, Folder 1509)
  - Federal Grant Restrictions Head Start (Box 36, Folder 1510)
  - Federal Grant Restrictions Job Training Partnership Act (Box 36, Folder 1511)
  - Federal Grant Restrictions Community Development Block Grant (Box 36, Folder 1512)
  - Federal Grant Restrictions AFDC/Welfare (Box 36, Folder 1513)
  - Federal Grant Restrictions Community Action Program (CAPS, CSBG), 1981-1985 (Box 36, Folder 1514)
  - Federal Grant Restrictions Community Action Program (CAPS, CSBG), 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 1515)
  - Federal Grant Restrictions Community Action Program (CAPS, CSBG), 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 1516)
  - Federal Grant Restrictions Community Action Program (CAPS, CSBG), 1990-1996 (Box 36, Folder 1517)
- Series XXIX: Press
  - News Clippings, 1983-1988 (Box 36, Folder 1518)
  - California Lawsuit, 1986-1988 (Box 36, Folder 1519)
  - Purge Case, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 1520)
  - News Clippings, 1989-1996 (Box 36, Folder 1521)
  - Human SERVE Press Releases, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 1522)
  - Human SERVE Press Releases, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 1523)
  - Human SERVE Press Releases, 1990-1991 (Box 36, Folder 1524)
  - Human SERVE Press Releases Turnout, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 1525)
  - Human SERVE Press Releases, 1992-1996 (Box 36, Folder 1526)
  - Negative, 1983-1993 (Box 36, Folder 1527)
  - News Pieces Mentioning Human SERVE, 1986-1996 (Box 36, Folder 1528)
  - News Clippings State Programs, 1990-1992 (Box 36, Folder 1529)
  - Press List, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 1530)
  - Positive NVRA Post Election, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 1531)
  - General Voter Turnout, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 1532)
  - News Clippings Election News, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 1533)
  - Cartoons, 1990-1995 (Box 36, Folder 1534)
  - Pre-final Passage, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 1535)
  - Post-Passage, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 1536)
  - Anticipating Low Voter Turnout, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 1537)
  - Human SERVE NVRA Report, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 1538)
  - Motor Voter Coalition Press Conference, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 1539)
  - Syndicated Columns, 1989-1995 (Box 36, Folder 1540)
  - Opinions and Editorials, 1988-1996 (Box 36, Folder 1541)
  - ACLU (Box 36, Folder 1542)
  - The Albuquerque Tribune (Box 36, Folder 1543)
  - American Bar Association (Box 36, Folder 1544)
  - American Political Science Review (Box 36, Folder 1545)
  - American Prospect (Box 36, Folder 1546)
  - Anchorage Daily News (Box 37, Folder 1547)
  - The Ann Arbor News (Box 37, Folder 1548)
  - Arizona Daily Star (Box 37, Folder 1549)
  - Asbury Park Press (Box 37, Folder 1550)
  - Asheville Citizen-Times (Box 37, Folder 1551)
  - Associated Press (Box 37, Folder 1552)
  - The Atlanta Constitution (Box 37, Folder 1553)
  - The Atlantic Monthly (Box 37, Folder 1554)
  - Austin American-Statesman (Box 37, Folder 1555)
  - Baltimore Evening Sun (Box 37, Folder 1556)
  - Bangor Daily News (Box 37, Folder 1557)
  - Beacon (Box 37, Folder 1558)
  - Bergen Record (Box 37, Folder 1559)
  - Bill Moyers Production (Box 37, Folder 1560)
  - Birmingham News (Box 37, Folder 1561)
  - Body Politic (Box 37, Folder 1562)
  - Boston Globe (Box 37, Folder 1563)
  - Boston Phoenix (Box 37, Folder 1564)
  - Bozeman Daily Chronicle (Box 37, Folder 1565)
  - Broadcasting (Box 37, Folder 1566)
  - David Broder Articles (Box 37, Folder 1567)
  - The Buffalo News (Box 37, Folder 1568)
  - Bulletin (Box 37, Folder 1569)
  - Business Week (Box 37, Folder 1570)
  - The Californian (Box 37, Folder 1571)
  - Campaigns & Elections (Box 37, Folder 1572)
  - CBS News (Box 37, Folder 1573)
  - Charlotte Observer (Box 37, Folder 1574)
  - Charleston Daily Mail (Box 37, Folder 1575)
  - Chattanooga News-Free Press (Box 37, Folder 1576)
  - Chavis (Box 37, Folder 1577)
  - Chicago Defender (Box 37, Folder 1578)
  - Chicago Sun-Times (Box 37, Folder 1579)
  - Chicago Tribune (Box 37, Folder 1580)
  - Children's Express (Box 37, Folder 1581)
  - Christian Science Monitor (Box 37, Folder 1582)
  - Chronicle (Oregon) (Box 37, Folder 1583)
  - Chronicle of Philanthropy (Box 37, Folder 1584)
  - Cincinnati Enquirer (Box 37, Folder 1585)
  - Cleveland Plain Dealer (Box 37, Folder 1586)
  - CNN (Cable News Network) (Box 37, Folder 1587)
  - Columbian (Washington) (Box 37, Folder 1588)
  - Columbia Spectator (Box 37, Folder 1589)
  - Columbia University Record (Box 37, Folder 1590)
  - Columbia School of Social Work Newsletter (Box 37, Folder 1591)
  - Columbus Free Press (Box 37, Folder 1592)
  - Commercial Appeal (Memphis, Tennessee) (Box 37, Folder 1593)
  - Community Jobs (Box 37, Folder 1594)
  - Congressional Digest (Box 37, Folder 1595)
  - Congressional Quarterly (Box 37, Folder 1596)
  - Congressional Record (Box 37, Folder 1597)
  - Conservative Digest (Box 37, Folder 1598)
  - Connecticut (Box 37, Folder 1599)
  - Cottage Grove Sentinel (Box 37, Folder 1600)
  - County News (Box 37, Folder 1601)
  - The Courier-Journal (Louisville, Kentucky) (Box 37, Folder 1602)
  - Courier-News (New Jersey) (Box 37, Folder 1603)
  - Courier Post (New Jersey) (Box 37, Folder 1604)
  - Cox Newspapers (Washington, D.C.) (Box 37, Folder 1605)
  - Daily Astorian (Oregon) (Box 37, Folder 1606)
  - Daily Citizen-News (Dalton, GA) (Box 37, Folder 1607)
  - Daily Courier (Oregon) (Box 37, Folder 1608)
  - Daily and Sunday Freeman (Kingston, NY) (Box 37, Folder 1609)
  - The Daily Gazette (Box 37, Folder 1610)
  - Daily-Herald (Chicago) (Box 37, Folder 1611)
  - Daily Journal (Box 37, Folder 1612)
  - Daily News (Longview, Washington) (Box 37, Folder 1613)
  - Daily News (New York) (Box 37, Folder 1614)
  - Daily News-Record (Harrisonburg) (Box 37, Folder 1615)
  - Daily Oklahoman (Box 37, Folder 1616)
  - Daily Press (Utica) (Box 37, Folder 1617)
  - Daily Targum (Box 37, Folder 1618)
  - Dallas Morning News (Box 37, Folder 1619)
  - Dallas Times Herald (Box 37, Folder 1620)
  - Daytona Daily News (Box 37, Folder 1621a)
  - (Box 37, Folder 1621b Delaware State News)
  - Democrat and Chronicle (Rochester, NY) (Box 37, Folder 1622)
  - Democrat-Herald (Oregon) (Box 37, Folder 1623)
  - Democratic Left (Box 37, Folder 1624)
  - Detroit Free Press (Box 37, Folder 1625)
  - The Detroit News (Box 37, Folder 1626)
  - DISSENT (Box 37, Folder 1627)
  - Economist (Box 37, Folder 1628)
  - Election Administration Reports (Box 37, Folder 1629)
  - Encyclopedia of Social Work (Box 37, Folder 1630)
  - Enterprise (Oregon) (Box 37, Folder 1631)
  - Extra! (Box 37, Folder 1632)
  - The Fauquier Times (Box 37, Folder 1633)
  - FOCUS (Box 37, Folder 1634)
  - FORTUNE (Box 37, Folder 1635)
  - Fort Worth Star-Telegram (Box 37, Folder 1636)
  - Funding Citizen Participation (Box 37, Folder 1637)
  - Globe and Mail (Canada) (Box 37, Folder 1638)
  - GOVERNING Magazine (Box 37, Folder 1639)
  - Guardian (Box 37, Folder 1640)
  - Harper's Magazine (Box 37, Folder 1641)
  - Hartford Courant (Box 37, Folder 1642)
  - Herald & News (Oregon) (Box 37, Folder 1643)
  - Home News (New Jersey) (Box 37, Folder 1644)
  - Houston Chronicle (Box 37, Folder 1645)
  - Houston Post (Box 37, Folder 1646)
  - Huguenot and Highland Herald (Box 37, Folder 1647)
  - Human Services (Box 37, Folder 1648)
  - Ideas For Action (Box 37, Folder 1649)
  - Ifco News (Box 37, Folder 1650)
  - Illinois Politics (Box 37, Folder 1651)
  - Independent News (Eagle Point, OR) (Box 37, Folder 1652)
  - Indianapolis News (Indiana) (Box 37, Folder 1653)
  - The Indianapolis Star (Box 37, Folder 1654)
  - In These Times (Box 37, Folder 1655)
  - Investor's Business Daily (Box 37, Folder 1656)
  - Jewish Week (Box 37, Folder 1657)
  - Journal (Rhode Island) (Box 37, Folder 1658)
  - Journal American (King County, WA) (Box 37, Folder 1659)
  - Journal Inquirer (Connecticut) (Box 37, Folder 1660)
  - Journal-News (Rockland County) (Box 37, Folder 1661)
  - Journal Star (Peoria, Illinois) (Box 37, Folder 1662)
  - Journal Tribune (Augusta, ME) (Box 37, Folder 1663)
  - Kennebec Journal (Kennebec, ME) (Box 37, Folder 1664)
  - The Kentucky Post (Box 37, Folder 1665)
  - Knight-Ridder Chain (Box 37, Folder 1666)
  - Law Matters (Publication of the American Bar Association) (Box 37, Folder 1667)
  - Las Vegas Review-Journal (Box 37, Folder 1668)
  - Ledger-Enquirer (Box 37, Folder 1669)
  - Legal Times (Box 37, Folder 1670)
  - Legislative Gazette (Box 37, Folder 1671)
  - Lewiston Sun-Journal (Box 37, Folder 1672)
  - Liberal Opinion (Box 37, Folder 1673)
  - Los Angeles Daily Journal (Box 37, Folder 1674)
  - Los Angeles's Free Weekly (Box 37, Folder 1675)
  - Los Angeles Herald Examiner (Box 37, Folder 1676)
  - Los Angeles Times (Box 37, Folder 1677)
  - Lynchburg News & Advance (Virginia) (Box 37, Folder 1678)
  - MacNeil/Lehrer NewsHour (Box 37, Folder 1679)
  - Mail Tribune (Medford, Oregon) (Box 37, Folder 1680)
  - Maine Sunday Telegram (Box 37, Folder 1681)
  - Metuchen Voter (Box 37, Folder 1682)
  - Miami, Florida News (Box 37, Folder 1683)
  - Miami Herald (Box 37, Folder 1684)
  - Michigan Chronicle (Box 37, Folder 1685)
  - Milwaukee Journal (Box 37, Folder 1686)
  - The Mobilizer (Box 37, Folder 1687)
  - The Montana Standard (Butte, Montana) (Box 37, Folder 1688)
  - Montgomery Advertiser (Box 37, Folder 1689)
  - Monthly Review (Box 37, Folder 1690)
  - Mother Jones (Box 37, Folder 1691)
  - The Nation (Box 37, Folder 1692)
  - Nation's Cities Weekly (Box 37, Folder 1693)
  - National Civic Review (Box 37, Folder 1694)
  - National Journal (Box 37, Folder 1695)
  - National Journal & Congress Daily (Box 37, Folder 1696)
  - National Public Radio (Box 37, Folder 1697)
  - National Voter (Box 37, Folder 1698)
  - NBC (Box 37, Folder 1699)
  - New Pittsburgh Courier (Box 37, Folder 1700)
  - New Republic (Box 37, Folder 1701)
  - News (Port Orford, Oregon) (Box 37, Folder 1702)
  - News Journal (Wilmington, Delaware) (Box 37, Folder 1703)